beau-coup.com 2010-12-28

# Beau-coup Wedding Favors Security & Privacy Policy

home > Beau-coup wedding favors security & privacy policy

Beau-coup is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and using information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy. 

How we use information 

Our site does not store personal information we collect in order to process transactions for commercial purposes. Contact information (email address, telephone number, address, etc.) from the order form is used to send your orders and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary. Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc.) that is collected is used only to bill you for products and services and not stored. Information collected on any of our forms may only be used to contact you, whether in person or via automated emails in response to your form submission. 

Cookies 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They make it possible for us to store contents of your shopping box until you are ready to check out and recognize your browser when you visit. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during checkout. In order to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user, your browser must be set to accept cookies. 

How we collect information 

This site uses a secure server (SSL) certified by Thawte to encrypt all of your personal information. We use strong security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our records. 

Your agreement 

By using our web site or purchasing a product from us, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. We may from time to time update this policy. We will post any changes to our policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. 

Commitment to customer service 

Beau-coup is committed to quality customer experience. We are constantly reviewing your feedback to improve and enhance your shopping experience. You can tell us what you think by sending us an e-mail or contacting our customer care department at 1-877-988-2328. 

Authorized third parties 

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, an industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information about the user is collected or used in this process.

You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative's website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) website. You may [opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of this data collection. 

We also work with a third party to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic and other advertising statistics. Where authorized by us, this third party may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is transferred to this third party.
